<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Posts on NetDevOps Space</title><link>https://netdevops.space/posts/</link><description>Recent content in Posts on NetDevOps Space</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Tue, 26 Jan 2021 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://netdevops.space/posts/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Awesome Folks and their projects</title><link>https://netdevops.space/posts/awesome/</link><pubDate>Tue, 26 Jan 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://netdevops.space/posts/awesome/</guid><description>You have probably come across the awesome list, where various interesting projects and links to it are published. It should be noted that all these projects are done by people who contribute a lot to their development. So I decided to make a similar list - Awesome Folks, and focus on the people of our community and their projects.
The list will be updated and added to.
If you have a candidate you&amp;rsquo;d like to suggest, or if you yourself would like to be on this list, please email egaripov@netdevops.</description></item><item><title>Markdown Samples</title><link>https://netdevops.space/posts/markdown-sample/</link><pubDate>Mon, 08 Jun 2020 08:06:25 +0600</pubDate><guid>https://netdevops.space/posts/markdown-sample/</guid><description>This is a sample post intended to test the followings:
A different post author. Table of contents. Markdown content rendering. Math rendering. Emoji rendering. Markdown Syntax Rendering Headings The following HTML &amp;lt;h1&amp;gt;—&amp;lt;h6&amp;gt; elements represent six levels of section headings. &amp;lt;h1&amp;gt; is the highest section level while &amp;lt;h6&amp;gt; is the lowest.
H1 H2 H3 H4 H5 H6 Paragraph Xerum, quo qui aut unt expliquam qui dolut labo. Aque venitatiusda cum, voluptionse latur sitiae dolessi aut parist aut dollo enim qui voluptate ma dolestendit peritin re plis aut quas inctum laceat est volestemque commosa as cus endigna tectur, offic to cor sequas etum rerum idem sintibus eiur?</description></item></channel></rss>